[{"answer": "Anybody wanna tell me what we're waiting for", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "And who the fuck is that", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I've wondered that myself.  None of this answers my question, though...  Why bring me", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Who am I", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "That's righ", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Whatever it is it must be goddamned priceless", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Not so fast.  Who's that", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " Bad company..", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " What's going on", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " See what", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " You told him I was a cop", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " He asked you to", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " He asked you to", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You need to know a lot of shit, my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I saw you look off when my friend nodded his head.  I figured he wasn't pointing out a particularly rare shrub, and the rest was easy", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " Because that's what I would have done..", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I still am", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "That's right", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "When this whole thing started you made it clea", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "And I don't believe you..", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "It was at that", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I've seen a lot of people die before", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What is", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " Best beer in the world?  Budweiser for me, thanks", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "It isn't about money for me, not anymore", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " Yes I do", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "So you thought that maybe I'd grown too attached to this charade I've been playing, is that it", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Not to me, you know that", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " Gaelic", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I'm sure", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " my friend", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I know of him", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I'm a field agent", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Dark operations.  Wet work.  Kidnaping. Assassination", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "You were behind the door", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "You would have done that", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "What the fuck happened", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "You don't know?  Bullshit, you had her, there was no way out", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I know I don't need to say this to you, but I need to say it to you.  This is my job, I have to do it", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "No you don't, and you know it", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Why?  You've got more force of will than anyone I've ever seen.  You handle a gun like it's a part of you, you perform surgery on yourself without anesthesia...  And most amazing of all, you quit smoking, just like that", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Why then, my friend, don't you act like this is a job like any other?  Surely, if you are a hired gun, you realize that some times you just have to walk away without getting what you came for", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "And when you finish?  What then?  This package, whatever it is, do you give it to the that place?  Do you really think they deserve it", "docId": "ronin_early.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Do you have a good answer", "qsentId": 44}]